[
    {"question": "ويليام", "response": "ويليام"},
    {"question": "نامي", "response": "نامي"},
    {"question": "لوفي", "response": "لوفي"},
    {"question": "ايرين", "response": "ايرين"},
    {"question": "استا", "response": "استا"},
    {"question": "همتارو", "response": "همتارو"},
    {"question": "الويفيا", "response": "الويفيا"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "نويل"},
    {"question": "رايلي", "response": "رايلي"},
    {"question": "ال", "response": "ال"},
    {"question": "لاو", "response": "لاو"},
    {"question": "مادارا", "response": "مادارا"},
    {"question": "يوريتشي", "response": "يوريتشي"},
    {"question": "ايتاتشي", "response": "ايتاتشي"},
    {"question": "توبي", "response": "توبي"},
    {"question": "نوبارا", "response": "نوبارا"},
    {"question": "ليفاي", "response": "ليفاي"},
    {"question": "هاشيراما", "response": "هاشيراما"},
    {"question": "بوروتو", "response": "بوروتو"},
    {"question": "يوسوب", "response": "يوسوب"},
    {"question": "ريم", "response": "ريم"},
    {"question": "اوتشيها شيسوي", "response": "اوتشيها شيسوي"},
    {"question": "كيد", "response": "كيد"},
    {"question": "ميكاسا", "response": "ميكاسا"},
    {"question": "دانزو", "response": "دانزو"},
    {"question": "وينغ", "response": "وينغ"},
    {"question": "تينشيهان", "response": "تينشيهان"},
    {"question": "بيكوهان", "response": "بيكوهان"},
    {"question": "كازيكاجي", "response": "كازيكاجي"},
    {"question": "جيرايا", "response": "جيرايا"},
    {"question": "كازيكاجي", "response": "كازيكاجي"},
    {"question": "كوكومي", "response": "كوكومي"},
    {"question": "غيو", "response": "غيو"},
    {"question": "تشيو", "response": "تشيو"},
    {"question": "ساسوري", "response": "ساسوري"},
    {"question": "نيزوكو", "response": "نيزوكو"},
    {"question": "ميدوريا", "response": "ميدوريا"},
    {"question": "نيجي", "response": "نيجي"},
    {"question": "ليزا", "response": "ليزا"},
    {"question": "كاغويا", "response": "كاغويا"},
    {"question": "هينا", "response": "هينا"},
    {"question": "الوكا", "response": "الوكا"},
    {"question": "هيناتا", "response": "هيناتا"},
    {"question": "زينتسو", "response": "زينتسو"},
    {"question": "رينغوكو", "response": "رينغوكو"},
    {"question": "كورتا", "response": "كورتا"},
    {"question": "هيسوكا", "response": "هيسوكا"},
    {"question": "انوس", "response": "انوس"},
    {"question": "بياكوغان", "response": "بياكوغان"},
    {"question": "شوكو", "response": "شوكو"},
    {"question": "ديكو", "response": "ديكو"},
    {"question": "يامي", "response": "يامي"},
    {"question": "فانجانس", "response": "فانجانس"},
    {"question": "يوليوس", "response": "يوليوس"},
    {"question": "تسوموغو", "response": "تسوموغو"},
    {"question": "نانامي", "response": "نانامي"},
    {"question": "ايزن", "response": "ايزن"},
    {"question": "زاراكي", "response": "زاراكي"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "اوراهارا"},
    {"question": "اينوي", "response": "اينوي"},
    {"question": "غوهان", "response": "غوهان"},
    {"question": "كيريلين", "response": "كيريلين"},
    {"question": "هيناتسورو", "response": "هيناتسورو"},
    {"question": "ريتشيل", "response": "ريتشيل"},
    {"question": "لوفي", "response": "لوفي"},
    {"question": "ناروتو", "response": "ناروتو"},
    {"question": "سابو", "response": "سابو"},
    {"question": "ايس", "response": "ايس"},
    {"question": "رايلي", "response": "رايلي"},
    {"question": "جيرايا", "response": "جيرايا"},
    {"question": "ايتاتشي", "response": "ايتاتشي"},
    {"question": "ساسكي", "response": "ساسكي"},
    {"question": "شيسوي", "response": "شيسوي"},
    {"question": "يوهان", "response": "يوهان"},
    {"question": "غوهان", "response": "غوهان"},
    {"question": "آيزن", "response": "آيزن"},
    {"question": "فايوليت", "response": "فايوليت"},
    {"question": "هانكوك", "response": "هانكوك"},
    {"question": "روبين", "response": "روبين"},
    {"question": "كاكاشي", "response": "كاكاشي"},
    {"question": "ريومو", "response": "ريومو"},
    {"question": "ريمورو", "response": "ريمورو"},
    {"question": "غوكو", "response": "غوكو"},
    {"question": "غوغو", "response": "غوغو"},
    {"question": "كيلوا", "response": "كيلوا"},
    {"question": "غون", "response": "غون"},
    {"question": "كورابيكا", "response": "كورابيكا"},
    {"question": "يوسكي", "response": "يوسكي"},
    {"question": "ايشيدا", "response": "ايشيدا"},
    {"question": "ايتيشغو", "response": "ايتيشغو"},
    {"question": "ميناتو", "response": "ميناتو"},
    {"question": "رينجي", "response": "رينجي"},
    {"question": "جيمبي", "response": "جيمبي"},
    {"question": "انوس", "response": "انوس"},
    {"question": "سايتاما", "response": "سايتاما"},
    {"question": "نيزيكو", "response": "نيزيكو"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "اوراهارا"},
    {"question": "تانجيرو", "response": "تانجيرو"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "نويل"},
    {"question": "يونو", "response": "يونو"},
    {"question": "لايت", "response": "لايت"},
    {"question": "إدوارد إلريك", "response": "إدوارد إلريك"},
    {"question": "ألّوكارد", "response": "ألّوكارد"},
    {"question": "ليفاي أكرمان", "response": "ليفاي أكرمان"},
    {"question": "زورو", "response": "زورو"},
    {"question": "سانجي", "response": "سانجي"},
    {"question": "شينوبو", "response": "شينوبو"},
    {"question": "ميدوريا", "response": "ميدوريا"},
    {"question": "باكوغو", "response": "باكوغو"},
    {"question": "شوتو", "response": "شوتو"},
    {"question": "أول مايت", "response": "أول مايت"},
    {"question": "سورا", "response": "سورا"},
    {"question": "نانامي", "response": "نانامي"},
    {"question": "كونان", "response": "كونان"},
    {"question": "كودو", "response": "كودو"},
    {"question": "ميوكي كودو", "response": "ميوكي كودو"},
    {"question": "اسكانور", "response": "اسكانور"},
    {"question": "غيومي", "response": "غيومي"},
    {"question": "ماكوتو", "response": "ماكوتو"},
    {"question": "ناتسو", "response": "ناتسو"},
    {"question": "شوبو", "response": "شوبو"},
    {"question": "ميدوريما", "response": "ميدوريما"},
    {"question": "ميتسوري", "response": "ميتسوري"},
    {"question": "سانيمي", "response": "سانيمي"},
    {"question": "هيبارا", "response": "هيبارا"},
    {"question": "ساسوري", "response": "ساسوري"},
    {"question": "باين", "response": "باين"},
    {"question": "هيدان", "response": "هيدان"},
    {"question": "كينجاكو", "response": "كينجاكو"},
    {"question": "كروكودايل", "response": "كروكودايل"},
    {"question": "سنبونزاكورا", "response": "سنبونزاكورا"},
    {"question": "روك لي", "response": "روك لي"},
    {"question": "مايت غاي", "response": "مايت غاي"},
    {"question": "مايت داي", "response": "مايت داي"},
    {"question": "غيتو", "response": "غيتو"},
    {"question": "غوجو", "response": "غوجو"},
    {"question": "فيجيتا", "response": "فيجيتا"},
    {"question": "غوجيتا", "response": "غوجيتا"},
    {"question": "غوكو بلاك", "response": "غوكو بلاك"},
    {"question": "اندفار", "response": "اندفار"},
    {"question": "ميدو عمي", "response": "ميدو عمي"},
    {"question": "رينيس", "response": "رينيس"},
    {"question": "رين", "response": "رين"},
    {"question": "ران", "response": "ران"},
    {"question": "ريم", "response": "ريم"},
    {"question": "ميكو", "response": "ميكو"},
    {"question": "اونوهانا", "response": "اونوهانا"},
    {"question": "شينجي", "response": "شينجي"},
    {"question": "تشون يون", "response": "تشون يون"},
    {"question": "سونغ جين وو", "response": "سونغ جين وو"},
    {"question": "جين مو وون", "response": "جين مو وون"},
    {"question": "تشو فيان", "response": "تشو فيان"},
    {"question": "زاو فان", "response": "زاو فان"},
    {"question": "جاي جو", "response": "جاي جو"},
    {"question": "دوم كانغ", "response": "دوم كانغ"},
    {"question": "سوه وونهوي", "response": "سوه وونهوي"},
    {"question": "تشون هاجين", "response": "تشون هاجين"},
    {"question": "بايك", "response": "بايك"},
    {"question": "يوني", "response": "يوني"},
    {"question": "ياسو", "response": "ياسو"},
    {"question": "امومو", "response": "امومو"},
    {"question": "ديانا", "response": "ديانا"},
    {"question": "جاكس", "response": "جاكس"},
    {"question": "اني", "response": "اني"},
    {"question": "جين سوهان", "response": "جين سوهان"},
    {"question": "لي هيون", "response": "لي هيون"},
    {"question": "ديابلو", "response": "ديابلو"},
    {"question": "زورو", "response": "زورو"},
    {"question": "تشوبر", "response": "تشوبر"},
    {"question": "ياماتو", "response": "ياماتو"},
    {"question": "كايدو", "response": "كايدو"},
    {"question": "فيجابانك", "response": "فيجابانك"},
    {"question": "دوفي", "response": "دوفي"},
    {"question": "ميهوك", "response": "ميهوك"},
    {"question": "سيزر", "response": "سيزر"},
    {"question": "بيروسبيرو", "response": "بيروسبيرو"},
    {"question": "جاك", "response": "جاك"},
    {"question": "كوين", "response": "كوين"},
    {"question": "كينغ", "response": "كينغ"},
    {"question": "جينتوكي", "response": "جينتوكي"},
    {"question": "ايتشيمارو", "response": "ايتشيمارو"},
    {"question": "اورواشيمارو", "response": "اورواشيمارو"},
    {"question": "ريومين", "response": "ريومين"},
    {"question": "ريوما", "response": "ريوما"},
    {"question": "موساشي", "response": "موساشي"},
    {"question": "ساساكي", "response": "ساساكي"},
    {"question": "ادم", "response": "ادم"},
    {"question": "بوسيدون", "response": "بوسيدون"},
    {"question": "جاك السفاح", "response": "جاك السفاح"},
    {"question": "زيوس", "response": "زيوس"},
    {"question": "شادو", "response": "شادو"},
    {"question": "نويل", "response": "نويل"},
    {"question": "فانيسا", "response": "فانيسا"},
    {"question": "اوراهارا", "response": "اوراهارا"}
]
